defra.gov.uk 2005-12-30

# Defra, UK - Defra website: privacy statement

If you are a user with general public and anonymous access the Defra website does not store or capture personal information, but merely logs the user's IP address that is automatically recognised by the web server. 

We do not use cookies for collecting user information (except in relation to online advertising - see below) and we will not collect any information about you except that required for system administration of our web server.

This privacy statement only covers the Defra website at http://www defra.gov.uk. This statement does not cover sub-domains (of the form http://subdomain.defra.gov.uk or http://www.subdomain.defra.gov.uk) - such addresses are typically used by web-based applications which may take different approaches to registration or logging of users - nor to links within this site to other websites (see hyperlinks to third party websites).

#### Online advertising

Defra uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage certain online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to [www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy).

#### Changes to this privacy policy

If this privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties. 

#### See also:

  * Help

  * Terms and conditions; copyright
